<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feature
      id="SRM.plugin"
      label="SRMPlugin"
      version="1.5.4">

   <description>
      SRM Plugin for Software Database Mining
   </description>

   <copyright url="http://www.example.com/copyright">
      [Enter Copyright Description here.]
   </copyright>

   <license url="">
      If you modify this Program, or any covered work, by linking or
combining it with FPGA (or a modified version of that
library), containing parts covered by the terms of EPL, the licensors of this Program grant you additional permission to convey the resulting work. Corresponding source for a non-source form of such a combination shall include the source code for the parts of FPGA used as well as that of the covered work.


SPMF GPL Exception

Section7 Exception

As a special exception to the terms and conditions of the GNU General Public License Version 3 (the &quot;GPL&quot;): You are free to convey a modified version that is formed entirely from this file (for purposes of this exception, the &quot;Program&quot; under the GPL) and the works identified at (http://www.philippe-fournier-viger.com/spmf/index.php?link=license.php) (each an &quot;Excepted Work&quot;), which are conveyed to you by Philippe Fournier-Viger and licensed under one the licenses identified in the Excepted License List below, as long as:

   1. You obey the GPL in all respects for the Program and the modified version, except for Excepted Work which are identifiable sections of the modified version.

2. All Excepted Works which are identifiable sections of the modified version, are distributed subject to the Excepted License.
         
If the above conditions are not met, then the Program may only be copied, modified, distributed or used under the terms and conditions of the GPL.

Excepted License List

    * Eclipse Public License: version 1.0
   </license>

   <plugin
         id="SrmPlugIn"
         download-size="0"
         install-size="0"
         version="0.0.0"
         unpack="false"/>

</feature>
